Hoffman Family Papers
© 2006 University of Connecticut
- Series V: Newspaper and Periodical Clippings, undated, 1936-1997
  - News, 1988 April, [1. William Safire, "Of Blacks and Jews," New York Times, editorial on Jackson's policy proposals in regards to Israel; 2. Jack Anderson, "Jackson speaks out strong for what he believes," unknown, reflections on the Jackson campaign; 3. unknown, "Jackson's 'Free Ride'," Extra!, analysis of media coverage of the Jackson campaign; 4. Associated Press, "Duke says mergers are mania," Daily News, Dukakis adopts a populist stance on corporate mergers; 5. Peter Johnson, "Reincarnation claim sets Moon apart," USA Today, report on Rev. Sun Myung Moon; 6. Maureen Dowd, "How Republicans View Bush: Some Faults, but 'a Class Act'," New York Times, Republican reflections on the Bush campaign; 7. Peggy L. Salvatore, "Democrats believe Jackson to be factor," Daily Intelligencer/Montgomery County Record, Democratic frontrunners are Jackson and Dukakis; 8. Mike Royko, "For candidate Jesse Jackson, black is really beautiful, Sunday Intelligencer/Montgomery County Record, editorial on how Jackson not pressured by the media or other candidates as much because he is black; 9. Dick Dahl, "The Massachusetts Miracle: did Dukakis make it or milk it?," In These Times, analysis of Dukakis' record in Massachusetts; 10. Kevin J. Kelley, "Will 'superdelegates' block Jackson nomination?," Guardian, fears that the Democratic party will refuse to nominate Jackson; 11. Chuck Wilbur, "Democrats: A whole new ballgame," Guardian, effect of the Jackson campaign on the Democratic Party; 12. Jay Levin, "Of This, That and Jesse," L.A. Weekly, editorial about the Jackson campaign; 13. Gregory Katz, "Thorny issue: Jackson and Jewish voters," USA Today, impact of Jackson's stance on Israel; 14. Mindy Fetterman, "Poll: Jackson gains as contender," USA Today, Jackson campaign is one of the frontrunners; 15. Walter Shapiro, "Taking Jesse Seriously," Time, analysis of the Jackson campaign and its chance of winning the election; 16. John B. Judis, "Hurdles in Jackson's presidential race," In These Times, potential problems for the Jackson campaign; 17. n/a, n/a, n/a, No Business As Usual Action Network; 18. n/a, n/a, n/a, letter from the spokesperson of Quest for Peace; 19. n/a, n/a, n/a, pg. 30 of Quest for Peace press release; 20. n/a, n/a, n/a, press release from Quest for Peace; 21. n/a, "For Jesse Jackson and His Campaign," The Nation, editorial in support of the Jackson campaign; 22. n/a, n/a, New York Times, poll of Democrats in New York on the presidential campaign; 23. Frank Lombardi, "Dukakis has company," Daily News, Dukakis' lead over Gore and Jackson is shrinking; 24. Doreen Carvajal and Kenneth J. Cooper, "Winning votes with opposite styles," Philadelphia Inquirer, differences between the Dukakis and Jackson campaigns; 25. David Moberg, "Jackson: scrutinizing the man, the message and the scrutinizers," In These Times, an analysis of the attacks made on the Jackson campaign; 26. Associated Press, "Bush Role on Toxic Gas Protection Described," New York Times, Bush sought to avoid Labor Department policy on workplace ventilation; 27. John Trinkel, "Jackson wins strong left support," Guardian, report on the radical left and the Jackson campaign; 28. Robin Toner, "Victory's Rarefied Air Is Bracing for Dukakis," New York Times, the rise of the Dukakis campaign; 29. Joe Klein, "Jesse Jackson For President?," unknown, analysis of the Jackson campaign and the potential for victory in November; 30. Marc Cooper, "Newspeak," L.A. Weekly, analysis of the media's treatment of the Jackson campaign; 31. Associated Press, "Pa. Pool favors Dukakis," Daily Intelligencer/Montgomery County Record, Dukakis is frontrunner in the Pennsylvania primary; 32. Associated Press, "Withdrawal readied by Gore," Daily Intelligencer/Montgomery County Record, narrowing of the Democratic contenders; 33. Salim Muwakkil, "Martin Luther King's legacy withstands test of time," In These Times, reflections on King's legacy in American politics; 34. Susan A. Douglas, "Time does Jackson in with subliminal message," In These Times, analysis of subtle racism in coverage of the Jackson campaign; 35. Associated Press, "Primary eve finds Democrats at odds," Daily Intelligencer/Montgomery County Record, Jackson and Dukakis campaign in Pennsylvania; 36. Jeffrey Hart, "Jesse Jackson is learning," Daily Intelligencer/Montgomery County Record, editorial about the progression of the Jackson campaign; 37. Bob Sanders, "Jackson support strong but spotty in Pennsylvania," Guardian, report on the results of the primary; 38. Associated Press, "Meese Is Seeking to Require Drug Testing in All Arrests," New York Times, Meese proposes policy shift in NYPD; 39. James Ridgeway, "The Duke of Evasion?," L.A. Weekly, analysis of Dukakis' foreign policy stance; 40. Steven Henshaw, "Bucks County Voters Go Big For Dukakis In Primary Tuesday," Delaware Valley News, report on the Delaware primary; 41. Bridget Wingert, "Duke knocks 'em out at Neshaminy High School," New Hope Gazette, Dukakis campaigns at a local high school; 42. Kathryn A. Marchocki, "Hoffman: Issues Today Similar to Those of '60s," Worcester Telegram, Hoffman gives lecture at Holy Cross University; 43. unknown, "Abbie Hoffman talks of '60s-'80s 'parallels'," unknown, Hoffman gives lecture at Holy Cross University; 44. Christopher Hitchens, "Minority Report," The Nation, Reagan administration on South Africa and Namibia; 45. n/a, n/a, n/a, News April 1988.] (Box 8:200)
  - News, 1988 May, [1. Jeff Greenfield, "Dole, the man without positions, is a poor one to assail media," unknown, analysis of the Dole campaign; 2. James North, "America's standing in the world community," New Patriot, analysis of Reagan's foreign policy; 3. n/a, n/a, New Patriot, Volume 1, no. 2, pgs. 1-5; 4. Deirdre Donahue, "His 'Journal' is an ode to the outdoors," USA Today, former President Carter builds a house in the woods; 5. Thomas Jaffe, "Streetwalker," Forbes, stock analysis; 6. Richard West, "Jackson was 'always one of the leaders'," USA Today, analysis of the Jackson campaign; 7. Judy Keen, "Dem duo not slowing campaigns," USA Today, Dukakis and Jackson campaign in Ohio; 8. n/a, "Election Line," USA Today, short pieces on the election; 9. Robert S. Boyd, "Bush-Dukakis could be a battle royal," Philadelphia Inquirer, predictions in the presidential campaign; 10. Jim Naureckas, "Is Kerry's contra-cocaine probe what it's cracked up to be?," Peace & Democracy News, Kerry's probe does not address the central issues behind the Iran-contra scandal; 11. n/a, n/a, USA Today, Inquiry section: ELECTION '88 analysis of the campaign positions; 12. Owen Ulmann, "Reagan based decisions on astrology, insiders say," Philadelphia Inquirer, Reagan in advanced stages of mental deterioration; 13. unknown, "The Jackson candidacy is no ordinary challenge," In These Times, analysis of the meaning of the Jackson campaign for American politics; 14. Dave Lindorff, "The primary irony: Jesse's New York loss was also a win of sorts," In These Times, implications of Jackson's strong showing in New York; 15. Alexander Cockburn, "Ashes & Diamonds," In These Times, criticism of Gore and media coverage of Cuba; 16. Associated Press, "Dukakis wins big in Ohio, Indiana," unknown, report on the Ohio and Indiana primaries; 17. Larry Eichel and Robert S. Boyd, "Dukakis captures Indiana, Ohio," Philadelphia Inquirer, report on the Ohio and Indiana primaries; 18. Richard Benedetto, "Dukakis wins 2 primaries; seven to go," USA Today, report on the Ohio and Indiana primaries; 19. n/a, "Election Line," USA Today, summary of campaign news items on May 4th 1988; 20. Charles Green, "Tax returns for Jacksons show $200,000 income, 25% paid to IRS," Philadelphia Inquirer, report on Jackson's tax return; 21. John Trinkel, "Jackson focus of Debate at Conference," Guardian, Jackson discussed at a Solidarity conference; 22. Kevin J. Kelley, "Jackson radically altering political landscape," Guardian, impact of the Jackson campaign on American politics; 23. Richard Benedetto, "Candidates treat California Like last lap in the race," USA Today, campaigns wind down in the California primary; 24. Jonathan A. Bennett, "Bush supports greater workplace hazards," Guardian, Bush seeks to undo OSHA regulations; 25. Larry Eichel, "Dismissing party skeptics, Jackson says he's viable," Philadelphia Inquirer, Jackson claims that he could win the presidential election on the Democratic ticket; 26. Robert S. Body, "Disenchanted with Reagan, his Democratic flock heads home," Philadelphia Inquirer, Reagan democrats return to the party fold; 27. Andrew Cassel, "Jackson stressing larger goals over presidency," Philadelphia Inquirer, Jackson campaign shifts towards influencing presidential race after the nomination is locked up by Dukakis; 28. Marc Cooper, "Newspeak," L.A. Weekly, analysis of media coverage of the campaign; 29. Richard Benedetto, "Dukakis hopes uncommitteds work 'magic'," USA Today, Dukakis banks on the centerist to win the campaign; 30. Associated Press, "Dukakis paid $25,892 in taxes last year," Bucks County Courier Times, Dukakis' taxes; 31. Tom Raum, "Bush 'troubled' by Meese allegations," Philadelphia Inquirer, Bush claims he has no intention of distancing himself from Meese; 32. n/a, "Election Line," USA Today, daily watch on campaign 5/6/88; 33. Fox Butterfield, "Dukakis," New York Times Magazine, analysis of the Dukakis campaign; 34. Peter Rapalus, "Environmental group rates Dukakis, Jackson over Bush," Philadelphia Inquirer, League of Conservation Voters releases report; 35. James Reston, "If Only Bush Would..." New York Times, editorial on press coverage of the campaign; 36. John Trinkel, "Jackson campaign energizes DSA," Guardian, impact of the Jackson campaign on the DSA's new national strategy; 37. Laura McClure, "Labor empowers Jackson and he returns the favor," Guardian, Jackson campaign receives strong support from the labor movement; 38. n/a, "Insights," L.A. Weekly, short news pieces on the California primary; 39. ] (Box 8:201)
  - News, 1988 June (Box 8:202)
  - News, 1988 July (Box 8:203)
  - News, 1988 August (Box 9:204)
  - News, 1988 August (Box 9:205)
  - News, 1988 September (Box 9:206)
  - News, 1988 September (Box 9:207)
  - News, 1988 October (Box 9:208)
  - News, 1988 October (Box 9:209)
  - News, 1988 November (Box 9:210)
  - News, 1988 November - December (Box 9:211)
  - News, 1989 (Box 9:212)
  - News, 1989 January - April (Box 9:213)
  - News, 1989 May -June (Box 9:214)
  - News, 1989 July - December (Box 9:215)
  - News, 1990 (Box 9:216)
  - News, 1991 (Box 9:217)
  - News, 1992 (Box 9:218)
  - News, 1993 (Box 9:219)
  - News, 1994 (Box 9:220)
  - News, 1995 (Box 9:221)
  - News, 1996 (Box 9:222)
  - News, 1997 (Box 9:223)
- Series VI: Artifacts, undated, 1955-1998
  - Awards for Abbie Hoffman, undated (Box 9:224)
  - Bumper Stickers, undated (Box 9:225)
  - Key to Maridor Motor Inn, Framingham, MA #109 (Box 10)
  - Key to Albion Hotel, Miami, FL #316 (Box 10)
  - McGovern Eagleton pen (Box 10)
  - Press Passes, undated (Box 9:226)
  - Political Pins (Box 10)
  - Posters, undated (Box 9:227)
  - Presentation from Labavitch, 1990 (Box 9:228)
  - Awards
    - 150th Anniversary Celebration Worcester medallion, 1998 (Box 11)
    - Award from Camp Mohican, undated (Box 11)
    - Diploma from Worcester Academy, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Worcester Academy Athletic Award for Tennis, 1955 (Box 11)
    - Bachelor's degree from Brandeis University, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Honorary law degree from New College of California, School of Law, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Worcester city key from Mayor Jordan Levy, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Wood plaque with "Hoffman called Man of Justice" article, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Wood plaque with People cover, 1989 (Box 11)
  - Clothing
    - Prayer Shawl (Box 12)
    - Red "Just Say No" T-shirt (Box 13)
    - White "Yippie Miami Beach" T-shirt (Box 13)
    - Green NBA large Celtics jacket (Box 13)
    - First National Bank of Boston bank bag (Box 14)
    - Pair of red, white, and blue socks (Box 14)
    - Black "Jack Hoffman Presents" T-shirt (Box 14)
    - Blue mortarboard with 36 political pins (Box 14)
    - Green "My Country Invaded Nicaragua..." T-shirt (Box 14)
    - Red "Just Say No" T-shirt (Box 14)
    - White "Red Sox 75 The Possible Dream" T-shirt (Box 14)
    - Red "Put the CIA on Trial" T-shirt (Box 14)
    - Green "Celtics Pride" T-shirt (Box 14)
  - Oversize posters
    - Abbie Hoffman Sold Out, 36" x 56" black and pink poster
    - The System is Falling Apart, 23" x 29" black and white poster
    - Abbie Hoffman 1936-1989, 21" x 25" red, white, blue, and black poster
    - El Salvador Another Vietnam, 18" x 24" brown, black, and white poster
    - Bette Midler, 19" x 21" orange, white, and black poster
    - Utamaro Casio, 13" x 25" orange, white, and black poster
    - Come Home, America, 13" x 24" red, yellow, orange, white, and blue poster (2)
    - Abbie Hoffman America Today, 14" x 22" red, black, and white poster (2)
    - Steal This Urine Test, 14" x 22" color poster - autographed by Abbie Hoffman and numbered "34/50"
    - Abbie Hoffman Live, 11" x 17" black and white poster
    - Bring Abbie Home, 11" x 17" red, white, blue, yellow, and black poster
    - Bring U.S. Together, 12" x 15" red, white, and black 1972 Chisholm campaign poster (2)
- Series VII: Audio/Visual Materials, undated
  - Family trip - No Abbie (Box 15:229)
  - Family at play - No Abbie (Box 15:229)
  - Thanksgiving (Box 15:229)
  - Family gathering - No Abbie (Box 15:229)
  - Boat trip - Phyllis as teen and Mom (Box 15:230)
  - Beach on boat - mostly Jack, no Abbie (Box 15:230)
  - Outdoor games - Jack, no Abbie (Box 15:230)
  - Jack and Abbie at beach - Phyllis as baby (Box 15:230)
  - Phyllis birthday and beach (Box 15:231)
  - Phyllis in bathing suit, outdoor party - no Abbie (Box 15:231)
  - Phyllis in bathing suit (Box 15:231)
  - Picnic and Phyllis at beach (Box 15:231)
  - John Hoffman outside big building (Box 15:232)
  - Ceremony at Synagogue (Box 15:232)
  - Trip to Corming, etc. - shots of Dad and Phyllis (Box 15:232)
  - Trip to Corming, etc. - shots of Dad and Phyllis (Box 15:232)
  - Family gathering - no Abbie (Box 15:233)
  - Family trip (Box 15:233)
  - Vacation Mexico - Phyllis, Mom, Dad (Box 15:233)
  - Vacation (Box 15:233)
  - Mexico - Phyllis (Box 15:234)
  - Phyllis in Mexico (Box 15:234)
  - Mrs. Hoffman and Phyllis in Europe (Box 15:234)
  - Mrs. Hoffman and Phyllis in Europe (Box 15:234)
  - Vacation in a tropical place - no Abbie (Box 15:235)
  - Mexico sites (Box 15:235)
  - Mexico (Box 15:235)
  - Mexico (Box 15:235)
  - Rome (Box 15:236)
  - Europe (Box 15:236)
  - Trip to Canada - no Abbie (Box 15:236)
  - Canada (Box 15:236)
  - Untitled (Box 15:237)
  - Phyllis, Mom, and Dad at beach in Mexico (Box 15:237)
  - Phyllis as teen - chew gum (Box 15:237)
  - Phyllis and Caddie - she dances (Box 15:237)
  - Jack in cap and gown - picnic (Box 15:238)
  - Jack's graduation picnic (Box 15:238)
  - Jack as teen in D.C. (Box 15:238)
  - Phyllis and Jack at a prom (Box 15:238)
  - Teen Abbie plays with baby on lawn (Box 15:239)
  - Niagara Falls with Phyllis (Box 15:239)
  - Phyllis dressed up, Jack throws snowball at camera (Box 15:239)
  - Somebody's wedding (Box 15:240)
  - John and family, Phyllis as bridesmaid (Box 15:240)
  - Bullfight (Box 15:241)
  - Orange Bowl (Box 15:241)
  - Tornado 1953 (Box 15:241)
  - Parade (Box 15:241)
  - Bad gate (Box 15:242)
  - NG - Gate problem (Box 15:242)
  - Out of focus (Box 15:242)
  - Cartoon (Box 15:242)
  - Graduation - Abbot (Box 15:244)
  - Untitled (Box 15:245)
  - Trip to NY State - no Abbie (Box 15:245)
  - Hoffman's 20th Anniversary Party (Box 15:245)
  - Family trip, early 50's - no Abbie (Box 15:245)
  - Battling the U-Boats (Box 15:246)
  - Untitled (Box 15:247)
  - Untitled (Box 15:248)
  - Big Fish (Box 15:249)
  - Untitled (Box 15:250)
  - The Little King (Box 15:251)
  - Puddy Pup (Box 15:252)
  - Dear Abbie! A Celebration cassette tapes (2) [use copy 1999-0106.253] (Box 15:253)
  - Sinbad the Sailor (Box 15:254)
  - Good shot of Mom and Dad at beach in Florida (Box 15:255)
  - Abbie as baby (Box 15:256)
  - Probus (Box 15:257)
  - Puss in Boots (Box 15:258)
  - Untitled (Box 15:259)
  - Untitled (Box 15:260)
  - Untitled (Box 15:261)
- Series VIII: Photographs, 1944-1989
  - Young Abbie Hoffman?, undated (Box 16:262)
  - Young Jack Hoffman?, undated (Box 16:263)
  - Abbie Hoffman?, 1972 (Box 16:264)
  - Abbie at 1972 Democratic National Convention?, 1972 (Box 16:265)
  - Abbie Hoffman (1), undated (Box 16:266)
  - Abbie Hoffman (2), undated (Box 16:267)
  - Abbie and Anita Hoffman, 1970 (Box 16:268)
  - Abbie and Jack Hoffman, undated (Box 16:269)
  - Abbie Hoffman and Johanna Lawrenson, 1982 (Box 16:270)
  - Abbie Hoffman and John Lennon, undated (Box 16:271)
  - Alexis Karklin Potemkin, undated (Box 16:272)
  - Class Photos, 1944 (Box 16:273)
  - Color Slides (13), undated (Box 16:274)
  - FBI Photos of Abbie Hoffman, 1973 (Box 16:275)
  - Frieda and Alan Brodsky (Box 16:276)
  - HBO Showcase "Conspiracy" Photos, 1987 (Box 16:277)
  - Hoffman Family Photos, undated (Box 16:278)
  - Jack Hoffman, 1964-1989 (Box 16:279)
  - Jack Hoffman, undated (Box 16:280)
  - Negative, undated (Box 16:281)
  - Photocopies of Photos, undated (Box 16:282)
  - William Kunstler and Allen Ginsberg, undated (Box 16:283)
  - Unidentified Photos, undated (Box 16:284)
  - 16" x 19" green photo album with gold star on front, undated (Box 16:284)